This video will explain to you how to make a rolled scarf in the hollow.
First, create a new fabric in the object window.
Then use the lifting plate tool to create a lifting plate of 2500x5mm.
Thickness of the lifting plate is 25mm.
Use the positioning tool in the 3D window.
Place the lifting plate in front of the scarf.
Then add a row of fixed needles to the top of the scarf.
Hold the lifting plate.
Then select the scarf plate.
Set the thickness of the lift plate to 3.
Pressure to 10.
Use the lift plate.
Simulation.
You can see that the scarf is automatically rolled up due to the pressure.
You can hold the lift plate.
Press the lift plate.
Hold the lift plate.
Pull the scarf.
The scarf will automatically roll up.
When the scarf is over, you need to pull it.
If it is a shorter version, you do not need to pull it manually.
You can add fixed needles to help adjust the flow.
Choose all the plates
Use the positioning tool to rotate it 90 degrees
Then move to the ground center
Choose the scarf plate and move to the ground center
simulation
The scarf plate will be neat under the weight
Next, improve the quality of the scarf
Click to confirm
Open the simulation
Adjust the shape of the scarf
Choose the shape plate
Adjust its conflict thickness to 25 mm
Organize the package shape of the scarf plate
Click to confirm
Next, choose the scarf plate
Increase the thickness of the scarf
To 3 mm
Open the simulation
Then adjust the conflict thickness to 3 mm
After the simulation is even
We again increase the conflict thickness to 3.5 mm
Open the simulation
After the simulation is even, you can delete the shape plate
Choose the scarf plate
Use the positioning tool to rotate it 90 degrees
Right click and place it in the ground center
simulation
Then delete the fixed needle in the middle
After the simulation
Right click to remove hardening
And the same process
Repeat the simulation
Then let's make the stack effect of three scarfs
Copy a scarf
Move the copied scarf to the ground center
Then drag it out with the positioning tool
Place it in the right place
Then copy a scarf plate again
In the same way, put it on top of the two scarfs.
Adjust its position.
Put two scarfs on top of the two scarfs before freezing.
Then turn on the simulation.
Make the upper scarf naturally fall on top of the two scarfs.
Freeze.
Next, enter the enamel window.
Enamel at the same time, check the effect of enamel.
The effect of the enamel is the same as the effect of the enamel at the same time.
The above is how we make a scarf in the kiln.
If you have any questions or other problems, please post them in the comments section.
Thank you for watching.